>> REPORTER:THIS IS SARAH
SOLCUM A SOCIAL MEDIA
CONSULTANT WHO LIVES IN THE
SHE WEARS HER GOOGLE GLASS
ALMOST EVERYWHERE SHE GOES
OVER THE WEEKEND HER
GLASSES GOT HER A LOT OF
ATTENTION AT A BAR IN SAN
FRANCISCO.
SHE CAPTURED SOME VIDEO OF
TO SHARE WHAT THE
EXPERIENCE OF WHAT IT IS
LIKE WHEN WEARING THEM.
>> REPORTER:SHE SAYS MOST OF
THE TIME WHEN SHE WEARS HER
GOOGLE GLASS IT IS RECEIVED
WELL BUT SOMETIMES IT CAN
BRING HER UN=WELCOMED
ATTENTION.
>>"IT WAS WEIRD, I
LITERALLY ENDED UP SAYING 'I
CAN'T AGAIN "
>> REPORTER:SARAH WAS OUT
WITH FRIENDS WHEN THEY
ENTERED A BAR IN THE HAIGHT
ASHBURY AREA IN SAN
>> REPORTER:THIS IS VIDEO
SHE CAPTURED
MINUTES AND TWO GIRLS THAT
WERE THERE STARTED SHOWING
A LOT OF ANIMOSITY
TOWARD ME BECAUSE I WAS
WEARING GOOGLE GLASS."
>>"I WALKED UP TO THE BAR
AND THEY WERE SHIELDING
THEMSELVES AND SAYING "OH
GOOGLE GLASS" KIND OF
NEGATIVE COMMENTS.
>>THEY WERE TRYING TO
SHIELD THEMSELVES AS IF I
WAS RECORDING THEM IT WASN'T
ON. I WASN'T USING IT. IT
WAS LIKE IF SOMEONE PULLED
OUT THEIR CELL PHONE AND
YOU WERE TRYING TO DODGE THE
CAMERA ON IT YOU KNOW. THEY
CLEARLY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THAT IT IS NOT ON RECORD
100% OF THE TIME."
>> REPORTER:THE ATTENTION ON
HER WEARING GREW AND GOT
MORE VOCAL
>>"AT THAT POINT I TURNED
ON THE VIDEO AND STARTED
>>"I KNOW I'VE BEEN SEEING
IN THE NEWS THE ANIMOSITY
TOWARD GOOGLE AND PEOPLE
BLOCKING GOOGLE BUSES BUT I
NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD BE A
TARGET OF THIS TECH GOOGLE
>>"YOU'RE KILLING THE CITY"
>> REPORTER:SARAH'S VIDEO
ALSO SHOWS SOME THINGS WE
BEING THROWN AND TOSSED
AROUND BAR LIKE THIS TOWELL.